(Penny:)Oh, I didn't tell you?
(Penny:)You're banished
from the Cheesecake Factory.
(Leonard:)- Why?
- Well, you have three strikes.
(Penny:)One, coming in. Two, sitting down.
(Penny:)And three, I don't like your attitude.
(Sheldon:)You can't do that. Not only is it a violation
of California State Law...
(Sheldon:)...it flies directly in the face
of Cheesecake Factory policy.
Yeah, no, there's a new policy:
No shoes, no shirt, no Sheldon.
(Howard:)I bet we could sell that sign
all over Pasadena.
- Penny, can I talk to you for a minute?
- Uh-huh.
(Penny:)- Hi.
- Hi.
(Leonard:)Look, here's the thing.
(Leonard:)I talked to Sheldon and he feels terrible.
(Leonard:)And he agrees that he was unreasonable
and out of line.
- Really? Well, that's great.
- Yeah.
Oh, just apologize to him, okay?
What? I'm not gonna apologize
to that nutcase.
(Leonard:)Come on, it's easy.
He'll even tell you what to say.
Don't you get it? You keep going along
with his insanity, you're encouraging him.